title,description,NER
Four people killed in Jashore road accident,"Four people were killed and another injured on Sunday in a collision between a truck and a private car at Dhopakhola Nimtala on Jessore-Benapole highway in sadar upazila, reports UNB. The deceased are Sadman, 27, son of Iqbal Chowdhury of Bayazid police station, Naim, 35, son of Ismail, Syed, 45, son of Badshah and Shahabuddin, son of Zahir Ahmed of the same area. According to highway police, five people were going to Benapole from Chattogram in a private car to buy cows. The private car collided with a Jashore-bound truck when it reached Dhopakhola at 12:25pm, leaving four people dead on the spot. Ali Newaz, who sustained injuries, was admitted to Jessore General Hospital. The driver managed to escape with the truck after the accident. Navaran highway police SI Md Wahid said the bodies were recovered.","[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Dhopakhola Nimtala', 'GPE'), ('Jessore-Benapole highway', 'FAC'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Sadman', 'PERSON'), ('27', 'DATE'), ('Iqbal Chowdhury', 'PERSON'), ('Bayazid', 'GPE'), ('Naim', 'PERSON'), ('35', 'DATE'), ('Ismail', 'PERSON'), ('Syed', 'PERSON'), ('45', 'DATE'), ('Badshah', 'PERSON'), ('Shahabuddin', 'PERSON'), ('Zahir Ahmed', 'PERSON'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Benapole', 'GPE'), ('Chattogram', 'GPE'), ('Jashore', 'GPE'), ('Dhopakhola', 'GPE'), ('12:25pm,', 'TIME'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ali Newaz', 'PERSON'), ('Jessore General Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Navaran', 'GPE'), ('Md Wahid', 'PERSON')]"
Three killed in Mymensingh road accident,"Three people, including a motorcycle rider, were killed in a road accident on the Mymensingh-Tangail highway in Rasulpur area under Muktagachha upazila of the district on Tuesday, reports BSS. The deceased were identified as motorcycle rider Selim, 25, Sabuj, 20, and Onta, 19. All the deceased are from Charipara village of Muktagachha upazila. Officer-in-charge (OC) of Muktagachha police station, Dulal Akand said the accident occurred when a speedy truck crushed with a motorcycle in the area around 8.00pm, leaving motorcycle rider Selim dead on the spot and injuring the other riders. Being informed, police rushed to the spot and recovered the dead body. The wounded were taken to Muktagachha Upazila Health Complex where on-duty doctors declared Sobuj dead. Onta was shifted to Mymensingh Medical College Hospital (MMCH) as his condition deteriorated. Later, he succumbed to his injuries at the hospital, the OC said. Police has detained the truck along with its driver, said the police officer.","[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mymensingh', 'GPE'), ('Rasulpur', 'GPE'), ('Muktagachha', 'GPE'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('BSS', 'ORG'), ('Selim', 'PERSON'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('Sabuj', 'PERSON'), ('20', 'DATE'), ('Onta', 'PERSON'), ('19', 'DATE'), ('Charipara', 'GPE'), ('Muktagachha', 'GPE'), ('Muktagachha', 'GPE'), ('Dulal Akand', 'PERSON'), ('around 8.00pm,', 'TIME'), ('Selim', 'PERSON'), ('Muktagachha Upazila Health Complex', 'ORG'), ('Sobuj', 'PERSON'), ('Onta', 'PERSON'), ('Mymensingh Medical College Hospital', 'ORG'), ('MMCH', 'ORG')]"
2 killed in Fatullah road accident,"Two passengers of a battery-run auto-rickshaw were killed when it collided with a covered van on the old Dhaka-Narayanganj highway adjacent to Masdair Amena Garments of Fatullah, reports UNB. The deceased have been identified as Afasar Uddin, 56 and Abbas Uddin, 48. Rakibuzzaman, officer-in-charge, Fatullah model police station confirmed the news. ""The locals rushed the injured to Narayanganj General Hospital where the duty physician declared two of them dead, "" he said. ""Locals held the driver of the covered van and handed him over to police."" At least 468 people were killed and 507 others injured in 432 road accidents across the country in April amid the nationwide lockdown, according to a report of Bangladesh Jatri Kalyan Samity. Besides, six more people were killed in eight accidents on rail tracks, 38 people were killed and nine others injured in 14 accidents on river routes while two others went missing during the month.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Masdair Amena Garments', 'FAC'), ('Fatullah', 'GPE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Afasar Uddin', 'PERSON'), ('56', 'DATE'), ('Abbas Uddin', 'PERSON'), ('48', 'DATE'), ('Rakibuzzaman', 'PERSON'), ('Fatullah', 'GPE'), ('Narayanganj General Hospital', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('At least 468', 'CARDINAL'), ('507', 'CARDINAL'), ('432', 'CARDINAL'), ('April', 'DATE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('38', 'CARDINAL'), ('nine', 'CARDINAL'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('the month', 'DATE')]"
"7 killed in three road accidents in Chattogram, Rangamati","At least seven people, including women and children, have been killed in three separate road accidents in Chattogram and Rangamati on Friday, reports UNB. About 22 more people were injured in these accidents. The accidents occurred in EPZ Steel Mills Bazar and Shikalbaha area of Karnafuli police station on Friday. According to police, three people, including a woman and a child, were killed when a bus overturned at Steel Mills Bazar area under EPZ police station around 12:00pm. Witnesses said a speeding bus hit a rickshaw at Sailo Road and crushed the pedestrians, losing its control while escaping at Friday noon. EPZ police officer-in-charge Utpal Barua said the mob detained the driver and helper of the bus and handed them over to the police. The bus was also seized. Meanwhile, three people were killed and at least 20 others injured in a head-on collision between two buses at Shikalbaha Chaumuhoni area of Karnafuli upazila. However, the identities of the injured were not immediately known. Police TI Anwar Azim said two buses collided while overtaking a CNG, injuring several passengers of the two buses. Two of them died. In Rangamati, a ninth-grader schoolgirl was killed in a head-on collision between a motorbike and a Jeep at Bangalhaliya's Shafipur area of Rajasthali-Chandraghona highway on Friday morning. The deceased was identified as Opruiching Marma, 18, daughter of Mongbaching Marma of Farua union in Bilachhari upazila. She is a ninth-grader student of Chitmaram High School. Two people including a motorcyclist were injured in the accident. Md Iqbal Bahar Chowdhury, officer-in-charge (OC) of Chandraghona police station, said legal action is being taken in this case. Police are searching for the jeep.","[('At least seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chattogram', 'GPE'), ('Rangamati', 'GPE'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('About 22', 'CARDINAL'), ('Shikalbaha', 'GPE'), ('Karnafuli', 'GPE'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Steel Mills Bazar', 'LOC'), ('EPZ', 'GPE'), ('around 12:00pm.', 'TIME'), ('Sailo Road', 'FAC'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('noon', 'TIME'), ('EPZ', 'ORG'), ('Utpal Barua', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('at least 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Shikalbaha Chaumuhoni', 'LOC'), ('Karnafuli', 'GPE'), ('Anwar Azim', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('CNG', 'PRODUCT'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rangamati', 'GPE'), ('ninth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Jeep', 'PRODUCT'), ('Bangalhaliya', 'GPE'), ('Shafipur', 'GPE'), ('Rajasthali', 'GPE'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('Opruiching Marma', 'PERSON'), ('18', 'DATE'), ('Mongbaching Marma', 'PERSON'), ('Farua', 'GPE'), ('Bilachhari', 'GPE'), ('ninth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Chitmaram High School', 'ORG'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Md Iqbal Bahar Chowdhury', 'PERSON'), ('Chandraghona', 'GPE')]"
ASI killed in Chattogram road accident,"An assistant sub-inspector (ASI) of police, Kazi Md Salahuddin, was killed in a road accident early Friday at Meheraj Khan Ghata in Chandgaon, Chattogram. He had been on the way to recover a consignment of local liquor when he was hit by a vehicle and killed. The deceased Kazi Md Salahuddin was the ASI of Chandgaon police station. He was the son of Kazi Nader Zaman of South Jaipur of the sadar thana in Lakshmipur district. Officer-in-charge (OC) of Chandgaon police station, Mustafizur Rahman, told Prothom Alo on Friday morning that Salahuddin had been on night duty in Maulvi Pukurpar, C&B and adjacent areas. He was tipped off about a black microbus (registration no. Dhaka Metro Cha 15- 3665) carrying local liquor from the hill tracts to Chattogram city. The OC further said Salahuddin and his driver constable Md Masum signalled the microbus to halt in front of the Meheraj Khan Ghata petrol pump in Chandgaon police station around 4:00 am. The microbus slowed down and the two members of the police went forward. But the microbus driver suddenly picked up speed and the vehicle hit Salahuddin. He fell to one side of the road, receiving injuries in his head, back and other parts of his body. Masum was injured too. OC Mustafizur Rahman said Salahuddin was taken to Chattogram Medical College Hospital. Masum is under treatment there. The microbus has been seized by the police, but the driver and his associates fled. Around 730 litres of local liquor was recovered from the vehicles. He said, a drive is on to arrest the driver and the others in the vehicle.","[('Kazi Md Salahuddin', 'PERSON'), ('early Friday', 'TIME'), ('Meheraj Khan Ghata', 'GPE'), ('Chandgaon', 'GPE'), ('Chattogram', 'GPE'), ('Kazi Md Salahuddin', 'PERSON'), ('Chandgaon', 'GPE'), ('Kazi Nader Zaman', 'PERSON'), ('South Jaipur', 'GPE'), ('Lakshmipur', 'GPE'), ('Chandgaon', 'GPE'), ('Mustafizur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('Prothom Alo', 'ORG'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Salahuddin', 'PERSON'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Maulvi Pukurpar', 'GPE'), ('Chattogram', 'GPE'), ('Salahuddin', 'PERSON'), ('Md Masum', 'PERSON'), ('Meheraj Khan Ghata', 'FAC'), ('Chandgaon', 'GPE'), ('around 4:00 am', 'TIME'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Salahuddin', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Masum', 'PERSON'), ('Mustafizur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('Salahuddin', 'PERSON'), ('Chattogram Medical College Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Masum', 'PERSON'), ('Around 730 litres', 'QUANTITY')]"
Mother-son killed in Sylhet road accident,"A woman and her two-year-old son died in a head-on collision between a private car and a bus on Dhaka-Sylhet highway in Sylhet on Sunday, reports UNB. Five others were injured in the accident. Police identified the deceased as Beauty Roy, wife of Gopesh Roy of Nabiganj upazila in Habiganj, and her son Rupak Roy. The accident occurred at Satmail around 1:30pm when the Dhaka-bound bus collided with the Sylhet-bound private car. Beauty Roy died on the spot and her son succumbed to his injuries while being taken to the hospital, said Monirul Islam, officer-in-charge of South Surma police station.","[('two-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Sylhet', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Beauty Roy', 'PERSON'), ('Gopesh Roy', 'PERSON'), ('Nabiganj upazila', 'ORG'), ('Habiganj', 'GPE'), ('Rupak Roy', 'PERSON'), ('Satmail', 'GPE'), ('around 1:30pm when the Dhaka', 'TIME'), ('Sylhet', 'GPE'), ('Beauty Roy', 'PERSON'), ('Monirul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('South Surma', 'GPE')]"
"RAB member, another killed in Gazipur road accident","Two people, including a member of Rapid Action Battalion (RAB-4), were killed when a microbus hit a stationary RAB vehicle on Dhaka-Mymensingh highway in Gazipur on Wednesday, reports UNB. The deceased were identified as Mohammad Khairul Islam, a member of RAB-4 and motor mechanic Liton Mia, said RAB SI Md Rakib. Other four injured are RAB’s senior warrant officer Md Shariful Islam, soldier Atiq, corporal Pradeep Kumar and motor mechanic Rifat. They have been airlifted to Dhaka CMH from Sreepur Hospital in Gazipur in a special helicopter, said Maona Highway police camp in-charge Kamar Hossain. SI Rakib said a microbus of RAB-4 went to Bhabanipur area of Gazipur sadar upazila and suddenly it stopped running due to mechanical fault on the way from Dhaka to Sreepur. Later, local mechanics Rifat and Liton were called to repair it. All of a sudden, another speedy microbus hit the RAB-4 stationary van from behind, leaving four RAB members and two mechanics were seriously injured. Later, they were taken to Al Hera Medical Center in Sreepur upazila for treatment where the duty physician declared Khairul Islam dead.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rapid Action Battalion', 'ORG'), ('RAB', 'ORG'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Gazipur', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Mohammad Khairul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('Liton Mia', 'PERSON'), ('RAB', 'ORG'), ('Md Rakib', 'PERSON'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('RAB', 'ORG'), ('Md Shariful Islam', 'PERSON'), ('Atiq', 'PERSON'), ('Pradeep Kumar', 'PERSON'), ('Rifat', 'PERSON'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Sreepur Hospital', 'FAC'), ('Gazipur', 'GPE'), ('Maona Highway', 'FAC'), ('Kamar Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('Rakib', 'PERSON'), ('Bhabanipur', 'GPE'), ('Gazipur', 'GPE'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Sreepur', 'GPE'), ('Rifat', 'PERSON'), ('Liton', 'PERSON'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('RAB', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Al Hera Medical Center', 'ORG'), ('Sreepur', 'GPE'), ('Khairul Islam', 'PERSON')]"
3 killed in Chattogram road accident,"At least three people, including two women, were killed after a truck hit an auto rickshaw head-on in Banshkhali upazila of Chattogram on Monday, reports UNB. Two other people were injured in the accident which occurred near Boilgaon area around noon. Police are yet to identify the victims. Banshkhali Police Station's duty officer assistant sub-inspector Jahangir Alam said three people died on the spot after the collision. The injured were hospitalised after rescue, he said.","[('At least three', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Banshkhali', 'GPE'), ('Chattogram', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Boilgaon', 'GPE'), ('around noon', 'TIME'), (""Banshkhali Police Station's"", 'ORG'), ('Jahangir Alam', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
Road accident kills two workers in Noakhali,"Two workers were killed as a pickup hit a rickshaw van on Begumganj-Chowmuhani road near Eklashpur Bazar area in Begumganj upazila of Noakhali on Monday night, reports BSS. The deceased were identified as Abdullah Al Mamun Akash, 17, resident of Katawalago village in Eklashpur union of the upazila and Nur Nabi, 16, from the same area. Locals said the accident occurred in the area when four workers were picking up sand in a rickshaw van. At one stage, a speedy pickup from the opposite direction hit the rickshaw van, leaving injured the duo seriously. The injured were taken to hospitals. One of the injured died at Noakhali Sadar Hospital. Another died at Dhaka Medical College Hospital. Officer-in-charge (OC) of Begumganj Model police station Muhammad Kamruzzaman Sikder confirmed the incident.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Begumganj-Chowmuhani road', 'FAC'), ('Eklashpur Bazar', 'GPE'), ('Noakhali', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('BSS', 'ORG'), ('Abdullah Al Mamun Akash', 'PERSON'), ('17', 'DATE'), ('Katawalago', 'GPE'), ('Eklashpur', 'GPE'), ('Nur Nabi', 'PERSON'), ('16', 'DATE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Noakhali Sadar Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Medical College Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Begumganj', 'GPE'), ('Muhammad Kamruzzaman Sikder', 'PERSON')]"
Couple killed in Meherpur road accident,"An elderly man and his wife were killed and five others injured in a road accident on Amjhupi-Garadove highway in Meherpur Sadar upazila on Tuesday morning, reports BSS. The deceased were identified as Abdus Sattar, 65, from Komorpur village of Mujibnagar upazila of Meherpur district and his wife Sara Khatun, 60. “Abdus Sattar and his wife fell victim to the accident when they were returning home after Sattar, being a cancer patient, received Chemotherapy from Rajshahi Medical College Hospital at around 8:00am,” confirmed by Meherpur sadar police station officer-in-charge (OC) Shahdara. Sara Khatun died on the spot when the driver of the microbus carrying them lost control over the steering and fell into a roadside ditch, said the microbus driver Redwan Ahmed who also is injured in the accident. Critically injured in the accident Abdus Sattar died on the way to Meherpur General Hospital. Police recovered the bodies and sent those to Meherpur General Hospital morgue.","[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Amjhupi-Garadove', 'FAC'), ('Meherpur Sadar upazila', 'GPE'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('BSS', 'ORG'), ('Abdus Sattar', 'PERSON'), ('65', 'DATE'), ('Komorpur', 'GPE'), ('Mujibnagar upazila', 'GPE'), ('Meherpur', 'GPE'), ('Sara Khatun', 'PERSON'), ('60', 'DATE'), ('Abdus Sattar', 'PERSON'), ('Sattar', 'PERSON'), ('Rajshahi Medical College Hospital', 'ORG'), ('around 8:00am,”', 'TIME'), ('Meherpur', 'GPE'), ('Shahdara', 'PERSON'), ('Sara Khatun', 'PERSON'), ('Redwan Ahmed', 'PERSON'), ('Abdus Sattar', 'PERSON'), ('Meherpur General Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Meherpur General Hospital', 'ORG')]"
"4 killed, 7 injured in Rangpur road accident","Four persons were killed and seven others injured in a road accident on the Rangpur-Dhaka highway in Mithapukur of Rangpur in the small hours of Friday, reports BSS. The deceased labourers were identified as Rafikul Islam, 45, Shahidul Islam, 50, and Abul Kalam, 45, from different villages of Lalmonirhat and Fazlul Karim, 65, of Sirajganj district. “The accident occurred when an onion-laden truck overturned as its driver lost control over the steering while overtaking another truck there around 1:00am,” said Yamin-Ud-Dowla, officer-in-charge (OC) of Barodorga highway police station. The Rangpur-bound truck from Bagerhat was carrying onions with some 11 labourers, mostly from Lalmonirhat and other northern districts, aboard when the accident took place killing one labourer on the spot and injuring 10 others. Police and personnel from nearby Shothibari Fire Service and Civil Defence Station rushed to the spot, rescued the injured persons and sent them to Rangpur Medical College Hospital (RpMCH) where three of them succumbed to their injuries till 1:00pm today. The wounded labourers –- Golam Mostafa, 35, Amir Hossain, 30, Amir Ali, 40, Babu Mian, 45, Guru Das, 40, Arjun, 25, and Rasel Milan, 30 -– are undergoing treatment at the RpMCH as their condition is still critical. “Driver and helper of the truck fled from the scene soon after the accident,” the OC said, adding that a case was filed in this connection with Mithapukur police station.","[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rangpur', 'GPE'), ('Mithapukur', 'GPE'), ('Rangpur', 'GPE'), ('the small hours of', 'TIME'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('BSS', 'ORG'), ('Rafikul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('45', 'DATE'), ('Shahidul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('50', 'DATE'), ('Abul Kalam', 'PERSON'), ('45', 'DATE'), ('Lalmonirhat', 'GPE'), ('Fazlul Karim', 'PERSON'), ('65', 'DATE'), ('Sirajganj', 'GPE'), ('around 1:00am', 'TIME'), ('Yamin-Ud-Dowla', 'PERSON'), ('Barodorga', 'GPE'), ('Rangpur', 'GPE'), ('Bagerhat', 'GPE'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lalmonirhat', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Shothibari Fire Service', 'ORG'), ('Civil Defence Station', 'ORG'), ('Rangpur Medical College Hospital', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('1:00pm today', 'TIME'), ('Golam Mostafa', 'PERSON'), ('35', 'DATE'), ('Amir Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('30', 'DATE'), ('Amir Ali', 'PERSON'), ('40', 'DATE'), ('Babu Mian', 'PERSON'), ('45', 'DATE'), ('Guru Das', 'PERSON'), ('40', 'DATE'), ('Arjun', 'PERSON'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('Rasel Milan', 'PERSON'), ('30', 'DATE'), ('RpMCH', 'FAC'), ('Mithapukur', 'GPE')]"
"One killed, 3 injured in Panchagarh road accident","A women was killed and three others injured in a road accident at Bypass intersection on Panchagarh-Debiganj highway in Boda upazila of the district Sunday, reports BSS. The deceased is Sufia Kathun, 50, wife of Raisul Islam of Mirpara village in Boda upazila. Officer-in-charge of Boda thana Abu Sayed Chowdhury said the accident occurred when a three-wheeler collided head-on with a sand-laden tractor at the Bypass intersection this afternoon, leaving Sufia dead on the spot and three other passengers injured. The injured are three-wheeler driver Joshim, 40, Dulu Sarker,60, and victim’s husband Raisul, 70. Boda thana police and fire service personnel, being informed, rushed to the spot and recovered the body and injured persons. Later, the injured were admitted to Rangpur Medical College Hospital for treatment.","[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bypass intersection', 'FAC'), ('Panchagarh', 'GPE'), ('Boda', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('BSS', 'ORG'), ('Sufia Kathun', 'PERSON'), ('50', 'DATE'), ('Raisul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('Mirpara', 'GPE'), ('Boda', 'GPE'), ('Boda', 'GPE'), ('Abu Sayed Chowdhury', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bypass', 'FAC'), ('this afternoon', 'TIME'), ('Sufia', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Joshim', 'PERSON'), ('40', 'DATE'), ('Dulu Sarker,60', 'PERSON'), ('Raisul', 'PERSON'), ('70', 'DATE'), ('Boda', 'GPE'), ('Rangpur Medical College Hospital', 'ORG')]"
Two musicians killed in Chattogram road accident,"Two of the country's leading musicians -- percussionist Hanif Ahammed and drummer Partha Guha -- died in a fatal road crash in Chittagong on Saturday morning, reports UNB. The accident occurred in the Mirsarai area of Chittagong around 5 am on Saturday when a group of musicians, including Hanif and Partha, and singer Beauty Khan, were on their way to Cox's Bazar for a concert. On Friday night, the artistes performed at a stage show in Chandpur. Police said that a microbus in which the artistes were travelling collided head-on with a truck coming from the opposite direction. The impact of the collision was such that Partha died on the spot while others sustained injuries. They were rushed to Chittagong Medical College Hospital, where Hanif was declared dead on arrival by doctors. The other injured -- vocalist Beauty Khan and musicians Nandan, Rahat, Pappu and Tauhid -- are currently being treated there. Hanif's elder brother Manik and musician Imran have confirmed the news of the fatal accident, while artistes from all over the country are mourning the ""tragic demise"" of Hanif and Partha on social media. Of the injured, doctors at the hospital said, the condition of Beauty Khan is critical. Both Hanif and Partha have played with almost all renowned singers and musicians in the country in the past two decades. Celebrated musicians, including Ankhi Alamgir, Kona, Elita Karim, Kornia, Muhin and Arfin Rumey, have expressed ""deep shock"" on social media over the tragic accident.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hanif Ahammed', 'PERSON'), ('Partha Guha', 'PERSON'), ('Chittagong', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('the Mirsarai area', 'LOC'), ('Chittagong', 'GPE'), ('around 5 am', 'TIME'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Hanif', 'PERSON'), ('Partha', 'PERSON'), ('Beauty Khan', 'PERSON'), (""Cox's Bazar"", 'FAC'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Chandpur', 'GPE'), ('Partha', 'PERSON'), ('Chittagong Medical College Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Hanif', 'PERSON'), ('Beauty Khan', 'PERSON'), ('Nandan', 'PERSON'), ('Rahat', 'PERSON'), ('Pappu', 'PERSON'), ('Tauhid', 'PERSON'), ('Hanif', 'PERSON'), ('Manik', 'PERSON'), ('Imran', 'PERSON'), ('Hanif', 'PERSON'), ('Partha', 'PERSON'), ('Beauty Khan', 'PERSON'), ('Hanif', 'NORP'), ('Partha', 'PERSON'), ('the past two decades', 'DATE'), ('Ankhi Alamgir', 'PERSON'), ('Kona', 'PERSON'), ('Elita Karim', 'PERSON'), ('Kornia', 'PERSON'), ('Muhin', 'PERSON'), ('Arfin Rumey', 'PERSON')]"
One killed in Panchagarh road accident,"A motorcyclist was killed in a road accident in Rousonbagh area on the Panchagarh-Jalashi highway of Panchagarh district on Wednesday. The deceased was identified as Masud Rana, 24, son of Nur Islam of Jalashi village in the district. Police said the accident occurred when an easy-bike knocked his motorcycle. In no time a sand-laden truck coming from opposite direction ran over Masud Rana, leaving him dead on the spot. Being informed, Sadar thana police rushed to the spot and recovered the body with the help of locals. Police seized the truck but the driver managed to flee. Sadar Thana officer-in charge Abu Akkas Ahamad confirmed the incident.","[('Rousonbagh', 'GPE'), ('Panchagarh', 'GPE'), ('Panchagarh', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Masud Rana', 'PERSON'), ('24', 'DATE'), ('Nur Islam', 'PERSON'), ('Jalashi', 'GPE'), ('Masud Rana', 'PERSON'), ('Sadar', 'GPE'), ('Sadar Thana', 'ORG'), ('Abu Akkas Ahamad', 'PERSON')]"
Road accident kills one in Narail,"A man was killed in a road accident in Kathadura area in Naragati thana of Kalia upazila of Narail on Monday, BSS reports. The deceased was identified as Md. Iqbal Molla, 40, son of one Sahabuddin Molla, from Chanderchar village in Kalia Upazila in the district. Police and witnesses said the driver of a human hauler, locally called Nosimon, was crushed and seriously injured when the Nosimon overturned on Monday around 10:00am. Locals rescued him and took him to Lohagora Upazila Health Complex where the physician declared him dead. Naragati thana officer-in-charge Roksana Khanom said a general diary was filed in this connection.","[('Kathadura', 'GPE'), ('Naragati', 'GPE'), ('Kalia', 'GPE'), ('Narail', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('BSS', 'ORG'), ('Md. Iqbal Molla', 'PERSON'), ('40', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sahabuddin Molla', 'PERSON'), ('Chanderchar', 'GPE'), ('Kalia Upazila', 'GPE'), ('Nosimon', 'PERSON'), ('Nosimon', 'PRODUCT'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('around 10:00am.', 'TIME'), ('Lohagora Upazila Health Complex', 'ORG'), ('Naragati', 'GPE'), ('Roksana Khanom', 'PERSON')]"
Two killed in Sylhet road accident,"Two people were killed after a truck plunged into a canal from a bridge in Jaintiapur upazila of Sylhet early Sunday. The deceased were identified as Ebadur Rahman, the driver of the truck, and Russel Ahmed, the driver’s assistant, both hailing from Jaintiapur. Police said the accident occurred around 5:30am on Sylhet-Tamabil road at Damri Bridge. The soil-laden truck fell into a canal from Damri Bridge, killing two people on the spot, said Mohamamd Ibrahim, officer-in-charge of Jointapur Police Station. On information, police and fire service members recovered the bodies with the help of locals around 7:30am.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jaintiapur', 'GPE'), ('Sylhet', 'GPE'), ('early Sunday', 'TIME'), ('Ebadur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('Russel Ahmed', 'PERSON'), ('Jaintiapur', 'GPE'), ('around 5:30am on Sylhet-Tamabil road at', 'TIME'), ('Damri Bridge', 'FAC'), ('Damri Bridge', 'FAC'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mohamamd Ibrahim', 'PERSON'), ('Jointapur Police Station', 'ORG'), ('around 7:30am', 'TIME')]"
Two killed in Rangpur road accident,"Two persons were killed in a head-on collision between a running motorcycle and a bicycle at Khalashpeer point on the Pirganj-Nababganj road in Pirganj upazila in Rangpur on Friday afternoon, reports BSS. “The accident occurred when the motorcycle hit the bicycle at Khalashpeer Hat point at 4:45pm. Both the motorcyclist and bicyclist were killed on the spot,” officer-in-charge (OC) of Pirganj police station Saresh Chandra said this evening. The deceased were identified as motorcyclist fire service personnel Asadul Haque, 25, of village Thakurdas Laksmipur and bicyclist Tofazzal Hossain, 65, of village Banspukuria in Pirganj upazila. The dead bodies were handed over to relatives of the respective victims after completing the necessary legal process. “None filed a case in this connection with Pirganj police station,” the OC confirmed at 7:20 pm.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Khalashpeer', 'LOC'), ('Pirganj', 'GPE'), ('Pirganj', 'GPE'), ('Rangpur', 'GPE'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('afternoon', 'TIME'), ('BSS', 'ORG'), ('Khalashpeer Hat', 'FAC'), ('4:45pm.', 'TIME'), ('Pirganj', 'GPE'), ('Saresh Chandra', 'PERSON'), ('this evening', 'TIME'), ('Asadul Haque', 'PERSON'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('Thakurdas Laksmipur', 'GPE'), ('Tofazzal Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('65', 'DATE'), ('Banspukuria', 'GPE'), ('Pirganj', 'GPE'), ('Pirganj', 'GPE'), ('7:20 pm', 'TIME')]"
3 killed in Cox’s Bazar road accident,"A road accident in Cox’s Bazar left three persons, including a child, dead and five others injured on Wednesday, UNB reports. The accident occurred on the Teknaf-Cox’s Bazar road around 10:00am. A passenger bus and an autorickshaw collided head-on, leaving three-wheeler passenger Salamat Ullah, 55, and his son Nazrul, 30, dead on the spot. Members of Hoikyang police outpost rescued the injured and took them to Palangkhali Goyalmara MFH Hospital and seized the bus. A young girl, aged about 8, died at the hospital, local sources said. Five of the victims have been shifted to Cox’s Bazar Sadar Hospital for better treatment. Hospital sources say two of them are in critical condition. Teknaf Model Police Station’s officer-in-charge Md Abdul Alim said they have so far received information about deaths of three persons in the accident.","[('Cox’s Bazar', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('the Teknaf-Cox’s Bazar', 'FAC'), ('around 10:00am', 'TIME'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Salamat Ullah', 'PERSON'), ('55', 'DATE'), ('Nazrul', 'PERSON'), ('30', 'DATE'), ('Hoikyang', 'GPE'), ('Palangkhali Goyalmara MFH Hospital', 'ORG'), ('about 8', 'DATE'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cox’s Bazar Sadar Hospital', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Teknaf Model Police Station’s', 'ORG'), ('Md Abdul Alim', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
"2 killed, 30 injured in Chandpur road accident","Two female passengers were killed on the spot and 30 more wounded on Monday afternoon, as a bus fell into a roadside ditch in Moutabari area under Shahrasti upazila of Chandpur, reports UNB. The deceased are Biva Rani Dash, 62, from Naora village of Shahrasti upazila and Geeta Rani Bhowmik, 65, from Cumilla's Nimsar area. Shahrasti police station officer-in-charge (OC) Md Abdul Mannan said the Chandpur-bound passenger bus of ‘Bogdad Paribahan’ carrying the victims fell into roadside canal after the driver lost control over steering, leaving two passengers dead on the spot and 30 others injured. Shahrasti station police and Shahrasti-Hajiganj fire service jointly conducted a drive to rescue the stuck passengers and immediately sent them to hospital, said OC Mannan. Shahrasti Upazila Health Complex's physician Jahanara Aktar said both the female passengers died on the spot. Three passengers including females are admitted to the hospital with severe injuries. Jahanara said 15 passengers have already left the hospital after receiving primary treatment.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('30', 'CARDINAL'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('afternoon', 'TIME'), ('Moutabari', 'LOC'), ('Shahrasti upazila', 'LOC'), ('Chandpur', 'GPE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Biva Rani Dash', 'PERSON'), ('62', 'DATE'), ('Naora', 'GPE'), ('Shahrasti', 'GPE'), ('Geeta Rani Bhowmik', 'PERSON'), ('65', 'DATE'), ('Cumilla', 'GPE'), ('Nimsar area', 'LOC'), ('Shahrasti', 'GPE'), ('Md Abdul Mannan', 'PERSON'), ('Chandpur', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('30', 'CARDINAL'), ('Shahrasti', 'GPE'), ('Shahrasti-Hajiganj', 'GPE'), ('Mannan', 'PERSON'), (""Shahrasti Upazila Health Complex's"", 'ORG'), ('Jahanara Aktar', 'PERSON'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jahanara', 'PERSON'), ('15', 'CARDINAL')]"
Two killed in Jashore road accident,"Two Motorcycle riders were killed and another two injured as two motorbikes collided head-on at Charavita area on Jashore-Narail road in Bagherpara upazila of the district on Tuesday evening, reports UNB. The deceased were identified as Md. Al Amin, 27, son of Anwar Hossain resident of Rajapur village in Lohagora upazila of Narail district and Yasin Rahman, 25, son of Mizanur Rahman of Teghori village in Bagherpara upazila under Jashore district. The accident took place at Charavita area on Jashore-Narail road when two motorbikes collided head-on, leaving Al Amin dead on the spot. Another injured Yasin died on the way to Khulna General Hospital, said Firoz Uddin, officer-in-charge (OC) of Bagherpara thana. Another injured two Motorcycle riders Kabil Sheikh, 26, and Sabbir Hossain, 17, were admitted in Jashore 250-bed general Hospital.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Charavita area', 'LOC'), ('Jashore-Narail', 'FAC'), ('Bagherpara', 'GPE'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('evening', 'TIME'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Md. Al Amin', 'PERSON'), ('27', 'DATE'), ('Anwar Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('Rajapur', 'GPE'), ('Lohagora', 'GPE'), ('Narail', 'GPE'), ('Yasin Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('Mizanur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('Teghori', 'GPE'), ('Bagherpara', 'GPE'), ('Jashore', 'GPE'), ('Charavita area', 'LOC'), ('Jashore-Narail', 'FAC'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Al Amin', 'PERSON'), ('Yasin', 'PERSON'), ('Khulna General Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Firoz Uddin', 'PERSON'), ('Bagherpara', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kabil Sheikh', 'PERSON'), ('26', 'DATE'), ('Sabbir Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('17', 'DATE'), ('Jashore', 'GPE'), ('250', 'CARDINAL')]"
4 killed in Sherpur road accident,"Four people were killed and two others injured after a truck hit a CNG-run auto-rickshaw on Sherpur-Jhenaigati road at Mirzapur in Sadar upazila of Sherpur on Sunday, reports UNB. Three of the deceased were identified as Selim Mia, 25, son of one Taher Ali of Chandgao Tingharia area of Nalitabari upazila, Roksana Begum, 30, wife of Rafiqul Islam of Naljora area and Jobed Ali, 25, son of one Yusuf Ali of Bandadhara in Sadar upazila. Abdullah Al Manun, officer-in-charge of Sadar Police Station, said the accident occurred around 8:45am when the truck hit an auto-rickshaw, leaving three people dead on the spot and injured three others. The injured were taken to Sherpur District Hospital where another victim succumbed to the injuries later. Five of the victims were passengers of the auto-rickshaw going to Sherpur from Jhenaigati. Traffic remained suspended for some time after the accident. Police rushed to the spot and rescued the victims after the accident. Police also seized the bus but could not arrest the driver of the truck as he fled the scene.","[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sherpur', 'GPE'), ('Mirzapur', 'GPE'), ('Sadar', 'GPE'), ('Sherpur', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Selim Mia', 'PERSON'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Taher Ali', 'PERSON'), ('Chandgao Tingharia area', 'GPE'), ('Nalitabari', 'GPE'), ('Roksana Begum', 'PERSON'), ('30', 'DATE'), ('Rafiqul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('Naljora', 'GPE'), ('Jobed Ali', 'PERSON'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Yusuf Ali', 'PERSON'), ('Bandadhara', 'GPE'), ('Sadar', 'GPE'), ('Abdullah Al Manun', 'PERSON'), ('Sadar Police Station', 'ORG'), ('around 8:45am when the truck', 'TIME'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sherpur District Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sherpur', 'GPE'), ('Jhenaigati', 'GPE')]"
2 killed in Hili road accident,"Two men were killed in a head-on collision between a motorcycle and a pickup van in Dinajpur’s Hili on Monday, UNB reports. The deceased were identified as Shakhawat Hossain, a final year student of Badarganj Government College and Najrul Islam from Badarganj upazila. Hakimpur Police Station’s in-charge Ferdous Wahid said Shakhawat and Najrul were returning to Badarganj from Hili on a motorcycle. They collided head-on with a pickup van. They died on the spot. Their bodies were recovered by police and taken to the police station.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dinajpur', 'GPE'), ('Hili', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Shakhawat Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('final year', 'DATE'), ('Badarganj Government College', 'ORG'), ('Najrul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('Badarganj', 'GPE'), ('Hakimpur Police Station’s', 'ORG'), ('Ferdous Wahid', 'PERSON'), ('Shakhawat', 'PERSON'), ('Najrul', 'PERSON'), ('Badarganj', 'GPE'), ('Hili', 'GPE')]"
One killed in Jashore road accident,"A man was killed as a truck hit his motorbike in the town’s New Khairtola area on Saturday night. The deceased was identified as Md. Sabuj Islam, 32, son of Sahidul Islam resident of Baluhar area in Kotchandpur upazila of Jhenidah district. Police and witnesses said, the accident took place at New Khairtola area on the Jashore-Jhenidah Road around 7.30pm when a truck hit his motorbike leaving him seriously injured. Locals rescued him and took to Jashore 250-bed general hospital where the physician declared him dead. He was heading towards his home at Baluhar area in Kotchandpur upazila from Jashore town. The body was sent to Jashore 250-bed general Hospital morgue for autopsy. Kotwali Model thana officer in charge (OC) Md.Moniruzzaman said,a General Diary (GD) was filed in this connection.","[('New Khairtola', 'LOC'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Md. Sabuj Islam', 'PERSON'), ('32', 'DATE'), ('Sahidul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('Baluhar', 'GPE'), ('Kotchandpur', 'GPE'), ('Jhenidah', 'GPE'), ('New Khairtola', 'LOC'), ('the Jashore-Jhenidah Road', 'FAC'), ('around 7.30pm when a truck', 'TIME'), ('Jashore', 'GPE'), ('250-bed', 'QUANTITY'), ('Baluhar', 'GPE'), ('Kotchandpur', 'GPE'), ('Jashore', 'GPE'), ('Jashore', 'GPE'), ('250', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kotwali Model', 'GPE'), ('Moniruzzaman', 'PERSON')]"
Woman killed in Meherpur road accident,"A 50-year-old woman was killed as a passenger bus rammed the motorbike she was sitting on from the behind in Meherpur city on Thursday night. The deceased Karfina Akhter was returning home at Amdah village of Meherpur sadar upazila with her husband Golam Mustafa. As per the witnesses, Mustafa and his wife were returning home by motorbike when a passenger bus hit their vehicle at College Mor (intersection) area. Kafrina fell on the street and her head was crushed. Locals took them to hospital where the physician declared Kafrina dead. The witnesses said they saw a 17 to 18-year-old boy, who was apparently driving the bus, flee immediately after the accident. Meherpur sadar police station officer-in-charge said, a police team has been sent to arrest the driver and his assistants.","[('50-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Meherpur', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Karfina Akhter', 'PERSON'), ('Amdah', 'GPE'), ('Meherpur', 'GPE'), ('Golam Mustafa', 'PERSON'), ('Mustafa', 'PERSON'), ('College Mor', 'FAC'), ('Kafrina', 'PERSON'), ('Kafrina', 'PERSON'), ('17 to 18-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Meherpur', 'GPE')]"
3 killed in Bandarban road accident,"Three people were killed and five others injured as a jeep locally called Chander Gari plunged into a ditch on Thanchi-Likri Road on Thursday morning, BSS reports. The deceased mostly labourers were identified as Md Ashu, hailed from Cox’s Bazar district, Md Hossain, from Chattogram and Payel Bom, from Thanchi Upazila. . Officer-in-charge of Thanchi Thana Md Sifuddin Anowar said the accident occurred as the driver of the Chander Gari lost his control over steering in Tin Kilometer area on the road. Ashu, Hossain and Payel Bom died on the spot. The Chander Gari was heading towards Thanchi. Injured people were admitted to Bandarban Sadar Hospital.","[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chander Gari', 'PRODUCT'), ('Thanchi-Likri Road', 'FAC'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('BSS', 'ORG'), ('Md Ashu', 'PERSON'), ('Cox’s Bazar district', 'GPE'), ('Md Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('Chattogram', 'GPE'), ('Payel Bom', 'PERSON'), ('Thanchi Upazila', 'GPE'), ('Thanchi', 'GPE'), ('Md Sifuddin Anowar', 'PERSON'), ('the Chander Gari', 'PRODUCT'), ('Tin Kilometer', 'LOC'), ('Ashu', 'PERSON'), ('Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('Payel Bom', 'PERSON'), ('The Chander Gari', 'PRODUCT'), ('Thanchi', 'GPE'), ('Bandarban Sadar Hospital', 'ORG')]"
Road accident kills couple in city,"A couple was killed in a road accident near Padma Oil gate on Airport Road in Dhaka on Monday morning. Sub inspector of Airport police station Moshiul Alam said the accident took place at around 7:15am. The couple, Akash Iqbal and Maya Hazarika, was on the way to their respective workplaces while a bus of Azmeri Paribahan hit their motorbike near the under construction terminal of the airport. Akash worked at Padma bridge project and Maya at Hotel Lake Castle. The couple died on spot. Police said the bus has been brought to the local police station and bodies were sent to Dhaka Medical College Hospital for autopsy.","[('Padma Oil gate', 'FAC'), ('Airport Road', 'FAC'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('Airport', 'FAC'), ('Moshiul Alam', 'PERSON'), ('around 7:15am.', 'TIME'), ('Akash Iqbal', 'PERSON'), ('Maya Hazarika', 'PERSON'), ('Azmeri Paribahan', 'ORG'), ('Akash', 'PERSON'), ('Padma', 'FAC'), ('Maya', 'PERSON'), ('Hotel Lake Castle', 'FAC'), ('Dhaka Medical College Hospital', 'ORG')]"
7 killed in Mymensingh road accident,"Seven people were killed after a bus hit an auto-rickshaw at Gachtala in Tarakanda upazila of Mymensingh on Sunday, reports UNB. The identities of the deceased could not be known immediately. Seven passengers of the auto-rickshaw were killed on the spot after a Netrakona-bound bus from Dhaka hit the Mymensingh-bound three-wheeler around 1:30pm, said Abul Khayer, officer-in-charge of Tarakanda police station. A firefighting unit from Mymensingh and police went to the spot and conducted the salvage operation. The bodies were taken to Mymensingh Medical College and Hospital.","[('Seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gachtala', 'GPE'), ('Tarakanda', 'GPE'), ('Mymensingh', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Netrakona', 'GPE'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Mymensingh', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('around 1:30pm, said', 'TIME'), ('Abul Khayer', 'PERSON'), ('Tarakanda', 'GPE'), ('Mymensingh', 'GPE'), ('Mymensingh Medical College and Hospital', 'ORG')]"
Four killed in Narsingdi road accident,"Four people were killed and one injured as a private car collided head-on with a bus at Dhaka-Sylhet highway in Belabo upazila in Narsingdi on Friday. The accident took place at Jangua area in Narayanpur union at around 4:00pm. Bhairab highway police station’s sub inspector Delwar Hossain said the name of the victims could not be confirmed immediately. Three of the victims were female and one male, he added. Police, witnesses and local people said the accident took place when a Sylhet-bound bus of Al Mobarak Paribahan tried to overtake another bus. Bhairab highway police later recovered the bodies from the car. Locals later took a female passenger of the car to Dhaka Medical College Hospital.","[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Belabo', 'GPE'), ('Narsingdi', 'GPE'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Jangua', 'GPE'), ('Narayanpur', 'GPE'), ('around 4:00pm.', 'TIME'), ('Bhairab', 'GPE'), ('Delwar Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sylhet', 'GPE'), ('Al Mobarak Paribahan', 'PERSON'), ('Bhairab', 'GPE'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Medical College Hospital', 'ORG')]"
4 sustain burns in Savar factory accident,"In a freak accident, four workers sustained burn injuries when hot water from a boiler spilled on them at a factory in Savar on Thursday, reports UNB. The injured workers have been identified as Rashedul, Hasan, Sandwip and Anwar. They are being treated at Enam Medical College and Hospital. The accident happened at SDS Yarn Dyeing factory in the Kuturia area of Savar’s Ashulia around 9:00 pm on Thursday. Hospital’s medical officer Nahiyan Binte Mojib said, “Rashedul and Hasan have been shifted to the hospital ICU as they sustained 60 per cent burns. The other two victims are being treated in the general ward.” Family members of the injured said that hot water from the factory’s boiler suddenly spilled on them, leading to the accident. Officer-in-Charge of Ashulia police station Kamruzzaman said that he was aware of the accident at the factory.","[('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Savar', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Rashedul', 'PERSON'), ('Hasan', 'PERSON'), ('Sandwip', 'PERSON'), ('Anwar', 'PERSON'), ('Enam Medical College and Hospital', 'ORG'), ('SDS Yarn Dyeing', 'ORG'), ('Kuturia', 'LOC'), ('Savar', 'GPE'), ('Ashulia', 'GPE'), ('around 9:00 pm', 'TIME'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Nahiyan Binte Mojib', 'PERSON'), ('Rashedul', 'PERSON'), ('Hasan', 'PERSON'), ('60 per', 'PERCENT'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ashulia', 'GPE'), ('Kamruzzaman', 'PERSON')]"
21 policemen injured in Brahmanbaria accident,"At least 21 policemen were injured as a bus hit a police van on Cumilla-Sylhet highway at Pirbari in sadar upazila early Monday, reports UNB. Mozammel Haque Chowdhury, additional superintendent of sadar circle police, said the accident occurred early in the morning when the bus of 'Econo Paribahan' hit the police van carrying 21 cops, leaving them injured. Among the injured, seven policemen were sent to Sadar General Hospital as their condition were stated to be critical. The policemen were returning to their respective police stations after performing their duties. Police arrested the bus driver and its helper from the spot.","[('At least 21', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cumilla-Sylhet', 'FAC'), ('Pirbari', 'GPE'), ('early Monday', 'TIME'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Mozammel Haque Chowdhury', 'PERSON'), ('early in the morning', 'TIME'), ('21', 'CARDINAL'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sadar General Hospital', 'ORG')]"
Police officer killed in Feni bike accident,"A newly appointed sub-inspector of police was killed while his friend sustained serious injuries when a speeding tractor crashed into their bike in Feni district on Tuesday night, police said, reports UNB. The accident occurred on the busy Chourasta-Maizdi Road at Chengarpole in Choumuhani of Feni district around 7:00pm when 31-year-old Mizanur Rahman Rony was on his way to join duty at the Begumganj Model Police Station. Sub-inspector of Sudharam Model Police Station, Yusuf, said the tractor hit the bike at a high speed, leaving Mizanur and his friend Zahidul Islam, the pillion rider, badly injured. The two were immediately rushed to Noakhali General Hospital, where Mizanur succumbed to his injuries around 9:00 pm, the officer said. “Zahidul has been shifted to a hospital in Dhaka for better treatment.” Mizanur, son of Sirajuddoula of Shonagazi upazila, was recently appointed as a sub-inspector at the Begumganj Model Police Station, said the officer-in-charge.","[('Feni', 'GPE'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Chourasta-Maizdi Road', 'FAC'), ('Chengarpole', 'GPE'), ('Choumuhani', 'GPE'), ('Feni', 'GPE'), ('around 7:00pm when 31-year-old Mizanur Rahman Rony was', 'TIME'), ('the Begumganj Model Police Station', 'FAC'), ('Sudharam Model Police Station', 'ORG'), ('Yusuf', 'PERSON'), ('Mizanur', 'PERSON'), ('Zahidul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Noakhali General Hospital', 'FAC'), ('Mizanur', 'GPE'), ('9:00 pm', 'TIME'), ('Zahidul', 'PERSON'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Mizanur', 'PERSON'), ('Sirajuddoula', 'PERSON'), ('Shonagazi', 'NORP'), ('the Begumganj Model Police Station', 'ORG')]"
35pc of accidents are on motorbikes,"There were 26 patients, injured in road accidents, in the corridor in front of the operating theatre of the National Orthopaedic Hospital and Rehabilitation Institute (Pangu Hospital) in the capital city last Saturday. Of these patients, 12 were injured in motorbike accidents. The hospital authorities say that a large percentage of the road injury cases are the victims of motorbike accidents nowadays. Persons researching on road accidents said that motorbike accidents are mainly caused by reckless speeding, attempts to overtake, repeated lane changes, violation of traffic rules and talking on the mobile phone while on the move. The number of deaths is also increasing due to low quality helmets or not wearing helmets at all. Pedestrians also fall victim to accidents due to reckless speed of motorbikes. Shamsul Alam, a member of the General Economics Department of the Planning Commission, was such a victim. He had an accident last Saturday evening while walking in the Crescent Lake area next to the Jatiya Sangsad Bhaban. He told Prothom Alo that he was hit by a speeding motorcycle while crossing the road. His right leg was broken in the accident. At Pangu hospital The National Orthopaedic Hospital and Rehabilitation Institute, better known as Pangu hospital, is the largest institute in the country for the treatment of fractured bones. Its official name is name is National Institute of Traumatology and Orthopedic Rehabilitation (NITOR). Inquiries at the hospital's emergency department revealed that 34 people have received treatment after being injured in road accidents till 1 pm on Saturday. Among them, 16 were the victims of motorcycle accidents. Some were driving the bikes, some were passengers riding pillion and some were pedestrians. According to the five registrar books of the emergency department, 2484 people received treatment at the hospital in the first 16 days of the new year. Of them, 585 were victims of road accidents. There is no mention of how many of them were the victims of motorbike accidents. However, Prof Abdul Gani Mollah, director of NITOR, told Prothom Alo that 35 per cent of the road accidents cases at NITOR are victims of motorcycle accidents. He said most of the patients come from outside the capital. In recent times, the number of people injured in motorcycle accidents while sharing rides is also increasing. University student Naimul Islam went to NITOR on Sunday with a fractured his arm. He frankly admitted that he had the accident due to over speeding while riding with a friend. He told Prothom Alo that his motorcycle was over-speeding and control on the sand on the road. Even the general motorcycle drivers are worried about reckless driving. Md Nayeem Hasan, who works for a private firm, returns his home to Mirpur from his office in Banani every night. He said that motorbikes and cars race each other. This has become a major cause of fear for the ordinary motorcyclists. How many vehicles, how many accidents? According to the Bangladesh Road Transport Authority (BRTA), the number of registered motorcycles in the country is more than 3.1 million, which is 68 per cent of the total vehicles. There are about 800,000 registered motorcycles in Dhaka alone. Outside of that a large part of the motorcycles are unregistered. According to the marketing companies, about 500,000 new motorcycles are sold in the country every year. The Accident Research Institute (ARI) of Bangladesh University of Engineering and Technology and the organisation for the advocacy of safe roads Nirapad Sarak Chai (Nischa) compile reports of accidents published in the media every year. According to Nishcha, there were 3232 road accidents in the country in 2020, of which 1,127 were motorcycle accidents. Of these, 29 per cent involved truck accidents and 22 per cent bus accidents. According to BUET's ARI, 336 people died in 288 motorcycle accidents in 2016. In 2020, the number of accidents raised to 1,008 and 1,097 people died in these accidents. A 2007 study by the World Health Organization (WHO) found that wearing a good quality helmet reduces the risk of serious injury in a motorcycle accident by 70 per cent. And the risk of death is reduced by 40 percent. Regarding the trend of not wearing a helmets outside the big cities, the Assistant Inspector General of Police (Media and Public Relations), Sohail Rana, said that action is being taken in accordance to the law for not wearing helmets. Various awareness programmes are also being arranged. Ride sharing has increased In Dhaka, motorbike ride sharing has increased exponentially in the last few years. Many people who are not even registered with ride-sharing companies, also carry passengers on their motorcycles. ARI conducted a survey of the riders and passengers of 450 ride sharing motorcycles in 2020. It revealed that 50 per cent of the passengers suffer from insecurity regarding the driving. According to another survey conducted by the same organisation, 30 per cent of the drivers wear very low quality helmets. In only 2 per cent of the cases, riders are given ‘full face’ helmets. According to ARI's observation, the competition of ride-sharing motorcycle riders and the tendency to race ahead are the main causes of accidents. On Sunday, Prothom Alo sent e-mails to the authorities of three ride sharing apps asking the number of accidents of their vehicles. Uber did not disclose the number of accidents, but answered the question. They said they pay Tk 200,000 for death and permanent disability in an accident and a maximum of Tk 100,000 for hospitalisation. Uber said they encourage the use of the best quality helmets. Pathao (ride sharing app) did not reply to the e-mail. However, Maliha Malek, the managing director of Shohoj dot com, told Prothom Alo over mobile phone that they did not have any reports of the their ride-sharing app bikes having any accident. What are the riders and sellers saying? A review by a multinational motorbike marketing company has revealed that overtaking is one of the major causes of motorcycle accidents. Apart from this, fatigue and rushing are also the main reasons for the accidents. Reckless driving of buses, trucks, ‘human hauler’ passenger vehicles and cars , sudden lane changes, sudden turning and lane changing of non-motorised vehicles, sudden potholes in the road, high or low covers of manholes, unmarked speed breakers, carelessness of pedestrians and sudden movement of animals on the road are also some big reasons behind road accidents. For example, Akash Iqbal (26) and his wife Maya Hazarika (25) were killed when a bus of Ajmeri Paribahan hit them on Airport Toad in the capital yesterday. Top two executives of the two companies told Prothom Alo that sales of the motorcycles as personal vehicles are increasing in developing countries. Motorcycle sales will also increase in Bangladesh like Indonesia, Vietnam, Thailand and India. Public-private initiatives are needed to reduce the number of accidents. They also said that there is no effective system of training the motorcyclists in the country. Awareness and training initiatives should be taken in combination with the private sector. People should be encouraged to buy high-tech motorcycles with a good security systems. Shah Mohammad Ashiqur Rahman, the chief financial officer of Honda Bangladesh Limited, said the number of accidents had increased in Japan once. Later they reduced it with various measures. He said Honda provides the driving license on behalf of the governments in many countries. They are also providing training in Bangladesh. Plastic bowls in the name of helmets Sajjadul Bari, Director (Standards) of Bangladesh Standards and Testing Institution (BSTI), told Prothom Alo yesterday that BSTI does not have the facility to check the quality of helmets at present. However, all the helmets sold in the market are supposed to be manufactured and imported as per the standards prescribed by the BSTI. Due to the lack of surveillance by BSTI, one portion of the helmets sold in the market is basically just plastic bowls. Regarding the overall scenario, ARI’s director Hadiuzzaman told Prothom Alo that ensuring good quality helmets for both the bikers and the riders, reducing the competition among the drivers of ride sharing apps, raising awareness and strictly enforcing traffic laws can reduce motorcycle accidents.","[('26', 'CARDINAL'), ('the National Orthopaedic Hospital and Rehabilitation Institute', 'ORG'), ('Pangu Hospital', 'ORG'), ('last Saturday', 'DATE'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('nowadays', 'DATE'), ('Shamsul Alam', 'PERSON'), ('the General Economics Department', 'ORG'), ('the Planning Commission', 'ORG'), ('last Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Crescent Lake', 'LOC'), ('the Jatiya Sangsad Bhaban', 'GPE'), ('Prothom Alo', 'ORG'), ('Pangu', 'GPE'), ('The National Orthopaedic Hospital and Rehabilitation Institute', 'ORG'), ('Pangu', 'GPE'), ('National Institute of Traumatology and Orthopedic Rehabilitation', 'ORG'), ('NITOR', 'ORG'), ('34', 'CARDINAL'), ('1 pm', 'TIME'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('2484', 'CARDINAL'), ('the first 16 days of the new year', 'DATE'), ('585', 'CARDINAL'), ('Abdul Gani Mollah', 'PERSON'), ('NITOR', 'ORG'), ('Prothom Alo', 'ORG'), ('35 per', 'PERCENT'), ('NITOR', 'ORG'), ('recent times', 'DATE'), ('Naimul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('NITOR', 'ORG'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Prothom Alo', 'PERSON'), ('Md Nayeem Hasan', 'PERSON'), ('Mirpur', 'GPE'), ('Banani', 'GPE'), ('every night', 'TIME'), ('the Bangladesh Road Transport Authority', 'ORG'), ('BRTA', 'ORG'), ('more than 3.1 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('68 per', 'PERCENT'), ('about 800,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('about 500,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('every year', 'DATE'), ('The Accident Research Institute', 'ORG'), ('Bangladesh University of Engineering and Technology', 'ORG'), ('Nirapad Sarak Chai', 'PERSON'), ('Nischa', 'ORG'), ('every year', 'DATE'), ('Nishcha', 'ORG'), ('3232', 'CARDINAL'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('1,127', 'CARDINAL'), ('29 per', 'PERCENT'), ('22 per', 'PERCENT'), ('BUET', 'ORG'), ('ARI', 'ORG'), ('336', 'CARDINAL'), ('288', 'CARDINAL'), ('2016', 'DATE'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('1,008', 'CARDINAL'), ('1,097', 'CARDINAL'), ('2007', 'DATE'), ('the World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('WHO', 'ORG'), ('70 per', 'PERCENT'), ('40 percent', 'PERCENT'), ('Sohail Rana', 'PERSON'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('the last few years', 'DATE'), ('ARI', 'ORG'), ('450', 'CARDINAL'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('50 per', 'PERCENT'), ('30 per', 'PERCENT'), ('only 2 per cent', 'PERCENT'), ('ARI', 'ORG'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Prothom Alo', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Uber', 'ORG'), ('Tk 200,000', 'MONEY'), ('Tk 100,000', 'MONEY'), ('Uber', 'ORG'), ('Maliha Malek', 'PERSON'), ('Prothom Alo', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Akash Iqbal', 'PERSON'), ('26', 'DATE'), ('Maya Hazarika', 'PERSON'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('Ajmeri Paribahan', 'PERSON'), ('Airport Toad', 'FAC'), ('yesterday', 'DATE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Prothom Alo', 'ORG'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Indonesia', 'GPE'), ('Vietnam', 'GPE'), ('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Shah Mohammad Ashiqur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('Honda Bangladesh Limited', 'ORG'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Honda', 'ORG'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Sajjadul Bari', 'PERSON'), ('Bangladesh Standards and Testing Institution', 'ORG'), ('BSTI', 'ORG'), ('Prothom Alo', 'ORG'), ('yesterday', 'DATE'), ('BSTI', 'ORG'), ('BSTI', 'ORG'), ('BSTI', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('ARI', 'ORG'), ('Hadiuzzaman', 'PERSON'), ('Prothom Alo', 'ORG')]"
Road crash claims two in Gulshan,"Two workers of a pushcart were killed leaving two more injured as a pickup van hit them at Gulshan in the capital on Saturday. The deceased identified as Arif Uddin (32) and Abdur Rahman Babul (44), reports UNB. Sub-inspector (SI) Mohammad Nuruzzaman of Gulshan police station said the accident took place at 12.45 pm. Being informed, critically injured Arif and Babul were rushed to Dhaka Medical College Hospital where the on-duty physician declared them dead at around 2:45 pm. Injured worker Kashem said he along with the three other was going to Coca-cola from Kalachandpur carrying rubbish on the pushcart when a pickup van hit it near Kalachandpur crossing. The dead bodies kept at the DMCH morgue for autopsy.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gulshan', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Arif Uddin', 'PERSON'), ('32', 'DATE'), ('Abdur Rahman Babul', 'PERSON'), ('44', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Mohammad Nuruzzaman', 'PERSON'), ('Gulshan', 'GPE'), ('12.45 pm', 'TIME'), ('Arif', 'PERSON'), ('Babul', 'PERSON'), ('Dhaka Medical College Hospital', 'ORG'), ('around 2:45 pm', 'TIME'), ('Kashem', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Coca-cola', 'ORG'), ('Kalachandpur', 'GPE'), ('Kalachandpur', 'GPE'), ('DMCH', 'ORG')]"
Two Ansar men killed in Jashore road crash,"Two Ansar men on Friday were killed in as their motorcycle hit a stationed truck Abhaynagar upazila of Jashore, reports UNB. The deceased were identified as Shahadat Hossain, 38, of Gazipur’s Kaliakoir upazila, and Nazrul Islam, 34, of Kushtia’s Mirpur upazila. Shahadat Hossain was a member of Jashore Navaran Ansar Battalion and Nazrul Islam of Khulna's Elahipur Ansar Battalion. The incident occurred in Alipur area of Jashore-Khulna highway. Citing witnesses, police said that Shahadat and Nazrul were going to Jashore on a motorcycle. At around 1.30 pm in Alipur area of Abhaynagar upazila it rammed into the back of a truck parked on the highway leaving Nazrul dead on the spot. Locals rushed Shahadat to Abhaynagar Upazila Health Complex where the emergency department physician declared him dead. Nawapara highway police officer-in-charge (OC) Mohammad Abdullah said the driver managed to escape with the truck after the accident. Attempts were being made to arrest him. The bodies were sent to Jashore General Hospital morgue for autopsy. An unnatural death was registered at Abhaynagar police station.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ansar', 'NORP'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Abhaynagar', 'GPE'), ('Jashore', 'GPE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Shahadat Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('38', 'DATE'), ('Gazipur', 'GPE'), ('Kaliakoir', 'GPE'), ('Nazrul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('34', 'DATE'), ('Kushtia', 'GPE'), ('Mirpur', 'GPE'), ('Shahadat Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('Jashore Navaran Ansar Battalion', 'ORG'), ('Nazrul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('Khulna', 'GPE'), ('Elahipur Ansar Battalion', 'ORG'), ('Alipur', 'GPE'), ('Jashore', 'GPE'), ('Shahadat', 'PERSON'), ('Nazrul', 'PERSON'), ('Jashore', 'GPE'), ('around 1.30 pm', 'TIME'), ('Alipur', 'GPE'), ('Abhaynagar', 'GPE'), ('Nazrul', 'PERSON'), ('Shahadat', 'PERSON'), ('Abhaynagar Upazila Health Complex', 'FAC'), ('Nawapara', 'GPE'), ('Mohammad Abdullah', 'PERSON'), ('Jashore General Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Abhaynagar', 'GPE')]"
"Truck driver, helper killed in Naogaon road crash","Two people were killed in a head-on collision between a truck and a bus at Satihat Panchamitala in Naogaon’s Manda Upazila on Thursday afternoon, police said, UNB reports. The deceased were identified as truck driver Masud Rana, 28, from Rajshahi and helper Omar Russel, 20, from Noakhalli. Shahinur Rahman, Officer-in-charge (OC) of Manda Police Station, said a mini truck carrying poultry was heading towards Rajshahi from Naogaon and collided head-on with a passenger bus at Satihat Panchamitala in Manda in the afternoon. Two people in the truck died on the spot. No casualties have been reported from the bus. A case has been filed with Manda police station in this regard, the OC added.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Satihat Panchamitala', 'GPE'), ('Naogaon', 'GPE'), ('Manda Upazila', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('afternoon', 'TIME'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Masud Rana', 'PERSON'), ('28', 'DATE'), ('Rajshahi', 'GPE'), ('Omar Russel', 'PERSON'), ('20', 'DATE'), ('Noakhalli', 'GPE'), ('Shahinur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('Manda Police Station', 'ORG'), ('Rajshahi', 'GPE'), ('Naogaon', 'GPE'), ('Satihat Panchamitala', 'GPE'), ('Manda', 'GPE'), ('the afternoon', 'TIME'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Manda', 'GPE')]"
Mango trader killed in road crash,"A 50-year-old mango trader was killed when a truck he was travelling in crashed into a tree at Tebaria bypass in Natore early Tuesday, UNB reports. The deceased was identified as Selim Hawladar, a resident of Madaripur district. Three more persons sustained injuries in the accident that occurred after the truck driver lost control of the vehicle, police said. Locals rescued all the victims and rushed them to Natore Sadar Hospital, where Selim was declared dead on arrival. Abdul Hakim, officer-in-charge (investigation) of Natore police station, said no case has been filed in connection with the accident.","[('50-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Tebaria', 'LOC'), ('Natore', 'GPE'), ('early Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Selim Hawladar', 'PERSON'), ('Madaripur', 'GPE'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Natore Sadar Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Selim', 'PERSON'), ('Abdul Hakim', 'PERSON'), ('Natore', 'GPE')]"
2 motorcyclists killed in Chattogram road crash,"Two motorcyclists were killed and another was injured in a road accident at Economic Zone area in Mirsarai upazila of Chattogram district on Sunday night. The deceased were identfied as Zabed Hossain, 30 and his nephew Nazmul Hossain, 12 of the upazila. The accident occurred around 10:00 pm when the motorbike off the road after its rider lost control over it, leaving three people injured, said Shilbrata Barua, assistant sub-inspector of Chattogram Medical College and Hospital police camp. Later, they were taken to the hospital where the physicians declared the two dead.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Economic Zone', 'LOC'), ('Mirsarai', 'GPE'), ('Chattogram', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Zabed Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('30', 'DATE'), ('Nazmul Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('12', 'DATE'), ('around 10:00 pm', 'TIME'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Shilbrata Barua', 'PERSON'), ('Chattogram Medical College and Hospital', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
"Couple, new born granddaughter killed in Bogura road crash","A couple and their new born granddaughter were killed and three others injured as a bus collided head-on with a CNG-run auto-rickshaw in the district on Saturday, reports UNB. The deceased were identified as Ashraf Ali, 50, his wife Parul Khatun, 45, and their one and a half months old granddaughter Rezwan. The accident occurred at Hathibanddha of Shibganj Upazila around 9:00am when the Rangpur-bound bus of “Ahsan Paribahan” from Dhaka had a head-on collision with the Bagura-bound auto-rickshaw. Those three were killed on the spot, said Md Mizan, sub-inspector of Shibganj police station. The three injured were taken to Shaheed Ziaur Rahman Medical College and Hospital, he added. Fatal road accidents are common in Bangladesh. Road accidents during last Eid-ul-Fitr holiday rush claimed 323 lives in just 15 days, according to Bangladesh Jatri Kalyan Shamiti.","[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('CNG', 'ORG'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Ashraf Ali', 'PERSON'), ('50', 'DATE'), ('Parul Khatun', 'PERSON'), ('45', 'DATE'), ('one and a half months old', 'DATE'), ('Rezwan', 'PERSON'), ('Hathibanddha', 'GPE'), ('Shibganj Upazila', 'GPE'), ('around 9:00am when the Rangpur', 'TIME'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Bagura', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Md Mizan', 'PERSON'), ('Shibganj', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Shaheed Ziaur Rahman Medical College and Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Eid-ul-Fitr', 'DATE'), ('323', 'CARDINAL'), ('just 15 days', 'DATE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Jatri Kalyan Shamiti', 'PERSON')]"
"Dhaka road crash kills mother, injures daughter","A mother was killed and her daughter injured in the capital Friday night as a bus ran over them when they were crossing a road. The incident happened in front of the Suvastu NAZAR Valley Shopping Mall in Gulshan, reports UNB. The deceased was identified as Sheikh Fauzia Ripa, 42. The injured was a college student at BAF Shaheen College and was identified as Anisha, 18. According to witnesses, the pedestrians took the mother and daughter to the emergency unit of Dhaka Medical College where the on-duty physician declared Ripa dead at 10 pm. Anisha is currently undergoing treatment in critical condition at the hospital. Bacchu Miah, inspector of Dhaka Medical College Hospital police outpost, confirmed the death to UNB.","[('Friday', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('the Suvastu NAZAR Valley Shopping Mall', 'FAC'), ('Gulshan', 'GPE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Fauzia Ripa', 'PERSON'), ('42', 'DATE'), ('BAF Shaheen College', 'ORG'), ('Anisha', 'PERSON'), ('18', 'DATE'), ('Dhaka Medical College', 'ORG'), ('Ripa', 'PERSON'), ('10 pm', 'TIME'), ('Anisha', 'PERSON'), ('Bacchu Miah', 'PERSON'), ('Dhaka Medical College Hospital', 'ORG'), ('UNB', 'ORG')]"
2 die in Panchagarh road crash,"Two persons were killed and another one was injured in a collision between a covered van and a pick-up van on Panchagarh-Tentulia highway on Wednesday night, police said on Thursday. The deceased were identified as Rubel, 25, of Kalandiganj Boalmari in Tentulia, and Swapan, 22, of Phultala in Boda upazila, reports UNB. The accident occurred in the Buraburi area of Panchagarh’s Tentulia upazila. “A Panchagarh-bound covered van hit a pick-up van after its driver lost control of the vehicle. The collision left two persons dead on the spot,” said Abu Sayem, officer-in-charge of Tentulia Model police station. “The injured person has been admitted to a local hospital,” he said, adding that a probe “is underway”.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Panchagarh-Tentulia', 'FAC'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Rubel', 'PERSON'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('Kalandiganj Boalmari', 'GPE'), ('Tentulia', 'GPE'), ('Swapan', 'PERSON'), ('22', 'DATE'), ('Phultala', 'GPE'), ('Boda', 'GPE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Buraburi', 'GPE'), ('Panchagarh', 'GPE'), ('Tentulia', 'GPE'), ('Panchagarh', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Abu Sayem', 'PERSON'), ('Tentulia', 'GPE')]"
Two bikers killed in Naogaon road crash,"Two men returning home on a bike were crushed to death by a speedy truck on the Rajshahi-Naogaon highway in Bijoypur on Friday night. The deceased were identified as Saidur Rahman, 35, son of Nazir Uddin of Badalghata village under Manda Sadar upazila, and Alfaz Hossain, 35, son of Ashar Ali of the same village. Manda police station's officer-in-charge Shahinur Rahman said that the accident occurred around 10:00pm when the victims were returning home from work. ""A speedy truck hit the bike as its driver failed to spot them. The duo died on the spot after getting crushed under the wheels of the truck,"" he said. Local police rushed to the spot soon after being informed by passersby and sent the bodies to the local hospital morgue for an autopsy. ""The bodies have been handed over to their family members,"" the OC said. A case has been filed at Manda police station in connection with the accident.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rajshahi-Naogaon highway', 'FAC'), ('Bijoypur', 'GPE'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Saidur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('35', 'DATE'), ('Nazir Uddin', 'PERSON'), ('Badalghata', 'GPE'), ('Manda Sadar', 'GPE'), ('Alfaz Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('35', 'DATE'), ('Ashar Ali', 'PERSON'), ('Manda', 'GPE'), ('Shahinur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('around 10:00pm when the victims', 'TIME'), ('Manda', 'GPE')]"
2 killed in Gopalganj road crash,"At least two people were killed and three others injured in a road crash in Gopalganj's Kashiani as a microbus and a pickup van collided head-on, reports UNB. The deceased were identified as NRBC Bank minibus driver Zafar Hossain, 42, son of Erfan in Bakerganj, Barishal and the pickup van driver Imran, 35, son of Mosharraf Hossain of Kathi village under Gopalganj Sadar upazila. The accident occurred near Dhusar bridge in Kashiani upazila on the Dhaka-Khulna highway at around 2:45pm on Friday. Abu Naeem, inspector of Bhatiapara outpost of Faridpur's Bhanga highway police station, said a NRBC Bank microbus was going from Dhaka to Satkhira. The incident took place when the microbus collided head-on with a pickup van coming from the opposite direction in Kashiani upazila. The driver of the microbus Zafar Hossain died on the spot. Police and fire service members rescued the pickup van driver and took him to Kashiani Upazila Hospital where he died while undergoing treatment.","[('At least two', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gopalganj', 'GPE'), ('Kashiani', 'GPE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('NRBC Bank', 'ORG'), ('Zafar Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('42', 'DATE'), ('Erfan', 'GPE'), ('Bakerganj', 'GPE'), ('Barishal', 'GPE'), ('Imran', 'PERSON'), ('35', 'DATE'), ('Mosharraf Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('Kathi', 'GPE'), ('Gopalganj Sadar upazila', 'GPE'), ('Dhusar bridge', 'FAC'), ('Kashiani', 'GPE'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('around 2:45pm on', 'TIME'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Abu Naeem', 'PERSON'), ('Bhatiapara', 'GPE'), ('Faridpur', 'GPE'), ('Bhanga highway', 'FAC'), ('NRBC Bank', 'ORG'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Satkhira', 'GPE'), ('Kashiani', 'GPE'), ('Zafar Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('Kashiani Upazila Hospital', 'ORG')]"
"2 killed, 6 hurt in Thakurgaon road crash","Two persons were killed and six others injured in a head-on collision between a three-wheeler and an auto-rickshaw in the Pallibidyut area of Thakurgaon Sadar on Thursday afternoon. Police said on Friday that one of the deceased was a businessman from Bogura district. The identity of the others has not yet been known. Eyewitnesses said while one person died on the spot in the impact of the collision, seven others—all passengers of the two vehicles—sustained injuries. Local residents and fire service personnel rushed the victims to the nearby Adhunik Sadar Hospital, where one of the injured succumbed to his injuries. Md Rakibul Alam, resident medical officer of Sadar Hospital, said the condition of two of the injured was critical. “They have been sent to Rangpur Medical College Hospital for better treatment,” he said.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('three-wheeler', 'QUANTITY'), ('Thakurgaon Sadar', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('afternoon', 'TIME'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bogura', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Adhunik Sadar Hospital', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Md Rakibul Alam', 'PERSON'), ('Sadar Hospital', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rangpur Medical College Hospital', 'ORG')]"
Teen killed in Gazipur road crash,"A 13-year-old boy died and another person sustained serious injuries after their pickup van crashed into a truck on the Dhaka-Mymensingh highway in Gazipur on Thursday morning. The deceased has been identified as Maruf, the helper of the pickup van. The vehicle’s driver has been injured in the accident. Eyewitnesses said the pickup van was travelling at a very high speed and it hit the Mymensingh-bound truck from behind in the Member Bari area of Gazipur Sadar after its driver lost control of the vehicle. The impact of the crash was such that Maruf died on the spot, police said. “The severely injured driver has been admitted to Mymensingh Medical College Hospital,” Md. Kamal Hossain, Officer-in-Charge of Mauna Highway Police Station, said. The body of the helper has been sent to Shaheed Tajuddin Ahmed Medical College Hospital for an autopsy, the OC added.","[('13-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Gazipur', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('Maruf', 'PERSON'), ('Mymensingh', 'GPE'), ('Gazipur Sadar', 'GPE'), ('Maruf', 'PERSON'), ('Mymensingh Medical College Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Md. Kamal Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('Mauna Highway Police Station', 'ORG'), ('Shaheed Tajuddin Ahmed Medical College Hospital', 'ORG')]"
Road crash kills three in Bhola,"At least three people were killed and five others injured in a head-on collision between a passenger bus and an auto-rickshaw in Ginger Haat area on the Bhola-Charfashion road under Sadar upazila of the district Wednesday afternoon, reports BSS. The deceased were Aziz, 40, Miraj, 30, and Sohag, 12. Officer-in-charge (OC) of Bhala model police station Md Enayet Hossain told BSS that the bus left Bhola bus stand with passengers for Charfashion. On the way, an auto rickshaw collided head-on with the bus coming from opposite direction in the area around 3:00pm, leaving three people dead on the spot and wounding five others, he added. The injured were sent to Sadar Hospital while critically injured three of them were referred to Barisal Sher-e-Bangla Medical College Hospital, the OC said. Supervisor of Bhola Sadar Hospital physician Md Sirajuddin said the bodies were kept at hospital for autopsy.","[('At least three', 'CARDINAL'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ginger Haat', 'LOC'), ('Bhola-Charfashion', 'FAC'), ('Sadar', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('afternoon', 'TIME'), ('BSS', 'ORG'), ('Aziz', 'PERSON'), ('40', 'DATE'), ('Miraj', 'PERSON'), ('30', 'DATE'), ('Sohag', 'PERSON'), ('12', 'DATE'), ('Bhala', 'GPE'), ('Md Enayet Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('BSS', 'ORG'), ('Bhola', 'GPE'), ('Charfashion', 'FAC'), ('around 3:00pm,', 'TIME'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sadar Hospital', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Barisal Sher-e-Bangla Medical College Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Bhola Sadar Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Md Sirajuddin', 'PERSON')]"
Road crash claims two lives in Brahmanbaria,"At least two persons were killed and three others injured in a head-on collision between a microbus and a pickup van on the Dhaka-Sylhet highway in Budhanti union of Bijoynagar upazila early on Friday morning. One of the deceased has been identified as Roni Khondokar, 13, son of Ripon Khondokar of Shayestaganj in Habiganj. The accident occurred early this morning when the Sylhet-bound microbus hit the pick-up coming from the opposite direction, said Md Shah Jalal Alam, officer-in-charge of Highway Police. The bodies of the deceased have been kept at the Highway police station, the OC added. On Thursday, three persons were killed in an accident on the high-speed corridor when a car hit a stationary truck at around 6.45 am at Amtali in Bijoynagar upazila of Brahmanbaria.","[('At least two', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Budhanti', 'GPE'), ('Bijoynagar', 'GPE'), ('early on', 'TIME'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Roni Khondokar', 'PERSON'), ('13', 'DATE'), ('Ripon Khondokar', 'PERSON'), ('Shayestaganj', 'GPE'), ('Habiganj', 'GPE'), ('early this morning', 'TIME'), ('Sylhet', 'GPE'), ('Md Shah Jalal Alam', 'PERSON'), ('Highway Police', 'ORG'), ('Highway', 'FAC'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('around 6.45 am', 'TIME'), ('Amtali', 'GPE'), ('Bijoynagar', 'GPE'), ('Brahmanbaria', 'GPE')]"
"Husband, wife among three killed in road crash","A couple among three were killed and four were injured as a private car crashed into a parked truck on Dhaka-Sylhet highway in Bijaynagar upazila of Brahmanbaria on Monday morning. The deceased were identified as Md Sagar, 35, his wife Shirin Akhter and the driver of the car Bilal Sarkar, 35. The injured are Shirin’s wife Naba Akhter, sister Sumi Akhter, relatives Md Julhas, 28 and Md Nayon, 25. UNB adds: The accident occurred early this morning. “The car hit the stationary goods-laden truck on the high-speed corridor around 6.45 am, after its driver lost control of the speeding vehicle,” said Md Shahjalal Alam, officer-in-charge of Highway Police. “The impact of the crash was such that the driver and another occupant of the car died on the spot,” he said. The other four injured occupants were taken to Madhupur Upazila Health Complex in Habiganj, where physicians declared one of them dead on arrival. The condition of the other three is said to be critical, the officer said. “A probe has been ordered into the accident,” he added.","[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Bijaynagar', 'GPE'), ('Brahmanbaria', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('Md Sagar', 'PERSON'), ('35', 'DATE'), ('Shirin Akhter', 'PERSON'), ('Bilal Sarkar', 'PERSON'), ('35', 'DATE'), ('Shirin', 'PERSON'), ('Naba Akhter', 'PERSON'), ('Sumi Akhter', 'PERSON'), ('Md Julhas', 'PERSON'), ('28', 'DATE'), ('Md Nayon', 'PERSON'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('early this morning', 'TIME'), ('6.45 am', 'TIME'), ('Md Shahjalal Alam', 'PERSON'), ('Highway Police', 'ORG'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Madhupur Upazila Health Complex', 'FAC'), ('Habiganj', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
Youth killed in Naogaon road crash,"A man was killed in a road accident in Naogaon‘s Porsha upazila on Wednesday, UNB reports. The deceased was identified as Hafez Rubel, 28, son of one Mohsin Ali of Saraigachhi village under the same upazila. The accident occurred at Saraigachhi crossroad in the afternoon. Porsha Police Station’s officer-in-charge (OC) Shafiul Azam Khan said Rubel reached Saraigachhi crossroad on a motorcycle when it collided head-on with a three-wheeler. He was taken to Porsha Upazila Health Complex where the doctor declared him dead. OC Shaiful said that the three-wheeler was seized but the driver managed to escape. A case was filed in this regard.","[('Naogaon‘s', 'GPE'), ('Porsha upazila', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Hafez Rubel', 'PERSON'), ('28', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mohsin Ali', 'PERSON'), ('Saraigachhi', 'GPE'), ('Saraigachhi', 'GPE'), ('the afternoon', 'TIME'), ('Porsha Police Station’s', 'ORG'), ('Shafiul Azam Khan', 'PERSON'), ('Rubel', 'PERSON'), ('Saraigachhi', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Porsha Upazila Health Complex', 'FAC'), ('Shaiful', 'PERSON'), ('three-wheeler', 'QUANTITY')]"
Road crash kills three of a family in Mymensingh,"Three people of a family were killed and another injured as a pick-up van crashed into a truck on Dhaka-Mymensingh highway at Trishal upazila in Mymensingh in the early hours of Monday. Police sources said the accident took place in Raimoni area of the upazila around 1:30am on Monday. The deceased were Aman Ullah, 38, his sister Nazma Akhter, 32, and her daughter Lalmoni, 7, from Bagherchar village of Sadar upazila in Shrpur while the injured was Akram Hossain, 50, driver of the pick-up involving the accident. Officer-in-charge (OC) of Trishal police station Main Uddin confirmed the deaths. He said a goods-laden pick-up van, carrying three people of a family, was going to Dhaka. The vehicle hit a Dhaka-bound truck from behind in Raimoni area as the driver of the pick-up van lost control. The accident left three people of a family dead on the spot and the pick-up van injured critically. The injured driver has been sent to Mymensingh Medical College Hospital, the OC added.","[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Trishal', 'GPE'), ('Mymensingh', 'GPE'), ('the early hours of', 'TIME'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Raimoni', 'LOC'), ('around 1:30am on Monday', 'TIME'), ('Aman Ullah', 'PERSON'), ('38', 'DATE'), ('Nazma Akhter', 'PERSON'), ('32', 'DATE'), ('Lalmoni', 'PERSON'), ('7', 'DATE'), ('Bagherchar', 'GPE'), ('Sadar', 'GPE'), ('Shrpur', 'GPE'), ('Akram Hossain', 'PERSON'), ('50', 'DATE'), ('Trishal', 'GPE'), ('Main Uddin', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Raimoni', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mymensingh Medical College Hospital', 'ORG')]"
3 dead in Chapainawabganj road crash,"Three paddy field workers were killed and seven others injured in a head-on collision between a truck and an electric rickshaw in Nachole upazila of Chapainawabganj district on Saturday, reports UNB. The deceased were identified as Rezaul Karim, son of Yunus Ali, Tosiqul Islam, son of Tajemul, and Alauddin Haque, son of Nazrul Islam of Gomostapur upazila. The accident took place at Dhansuramor around 9:30am when the Nachole-bound truck carrying paddy hit the e-rickshaw coming from the opposite direction. The impact of the collision was such that the e-rickshaw overturned, and three died on the spot. Cops were alerted by passersby and a team from the local police station and fire station rushed to the spot and sent the injured to Nachole Upazila Health Complex. Five of the injured have been shifted to Rajshahi Medical College and Hospital as their condition is said to be critical, police said. A probe has been ordered into the accident, an official said.","[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nachole', 'GPE'), ('Chapainawabganj', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Rezaul Karim', 'PERSON'), ('Yunus Ali', 'PERSON'), ('Tosiqul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('Tajemul', 'PERSON'), ('Alauddin Haque', 'PERSON'), ('Nazrul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('Gomostapur', 'GPE'), ('Dhansuramor', 'GPE'), ('around 9:30am when the Nachole', 'TIME'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nachole Upazila Health Complex', 'ORG'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rajshahi Medical College and Hospital', 'ORG')]"
Child killed in Satkhira road crash,"An eight-year-old child was killed on Sunday morning in a road crash in Satkhira’s Shyamnagar, UNB reports. The deceased was identified as Maria Akhter, daughter of Habibullah of Burigoalini union and a second-grade student at Kalbari Government Primary School. According to locals, the child was playing by the roadside at Joliler Mor area where her parents were working. Suddenly a motor run van hit her causing serious injury. She was rushed to Shyamnagar Upazila Health Complex where she was declared dead by the physician. Locals managed to seize the van but its driver, Sushant escaped. Shyamnagar Police Station officer-in-charge (OC) Nazmud Huda said police were sent to the spot. Legal action will be taken if a complaint is received from the family of the deceased, he added.","[('eight-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('Satkhira', 'GPE'), ('Shyamnagar', 'GPE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Maria Akhter', 'PERSON'), ('Habibullah', 'PERSON'), ('Burigoalini', 'NORP'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Kalbari Government Primary School', 'ORG'), ('Joliler Mor', 'LOC'), ('Shyamnagar Upazila Health Complex', 'FAC'), ('Sushant', 'PERSON'), ('Shyamnagar Police Station', 'ORG'), ('Nazmud Huda', 'PERSON')]"
Road crash leaves three dead in Sylhet,"Three people were killed as a truck ploughed through a roadside motor workshop at Darbast bazar in Jaintapur upazila on Sylhet-Tamabil highway on Monday morning, reports UNB. The deceased were identified as Sohel Ahmed, Ashik Ahmed and Minhaz Uddin Sultan. The accident took place when a speeding Jaflong-bound truck ploughed through a motor workshop after the driver lost control of the vehicle, said Partha Ranjan Chakrabarty, sub-inspector (SI) of Jaintiapur police station. The bodies were sent to Sylhet MAG Osmani Medical College Hospital for autopsy. The accident took place a day after another deadly accident on the same highway in Jaintiapur upazila that left five people dead.","[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Darbast', 'GPE'), ('Jaintapur', 'GPE'), ('Sylhet', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Sohel Ahmed', 'PERSON'), ('Ashik Ahmed', 'PERSON'), ('Minhaz Uddin Sultan', 'PERSON'), ('Jaflong', 'GPE'), ('Partha Ranjan Chakrabarty', 'PERSON'), ('Jaintiapur', 'GPE'), ('Sylhet MAG Osmani Medical College Hospital', 'ORG'), ('a day', 'DATE'), ('Jaintiapur', 'GPE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL')]"
ASI killed in Bhola road crash,"At least one person was killed in a road crash in Bhola’s Borhanuddin upazila on Sunday, reports UNB. The deceased was identified as Aklima Akhter, 38, assistant sub-inspector (ASI) of Borhanuddin police station. Her husband Jasim Uddin is working as sub-inspector in Bhola Sadar police station. According to police, ASI Aklima went to Kunjerhat area on a motorcycle with constable Zakaria to investigate a complaint. On their way back to Borhanuddin police station, ASI Aklima fell off the motorcycle as Zakaria made a sudden break in an attempt to save a pedestrian crossing the road near at Kunjerhat bazar area. At this very moment, a speeding truck from opposite direction crushed ASI Aklima to death on spot, confirmed Borhanuddin police station’ Officer in charge (OC) Mazhar Amin. Police arrested the driver Azhar Khan as locals seized the deadly truck after the accident.","[('At least one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bhola', 'GPE'), ('Borhanuddin', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Aklima Akhter', 'PERSON'), ('38', 'DATE'), ('Borhanuddin', 'GPE'), ('Jasim Uddin', 'PERSON'), ('Bhola Sadar', 'GPE'), ('Aklima', 'PERSON'), ('Kunjerhat', 'LOC'), ('Zakaria', 'PERSON'), ('Borhanuddin', 'GPE'), ('ASI Aklima', 'PERSON'), ('Zakaria', 'PERSON'), ('Kunjerhat bazar', 'LOC'), ('ASI Aklima', 'PERSON'), ('Borhanuddin', 'GPE'), ('Mazhar Amin', 'PERSON'), ('Azhar Khan', 'PERSON')]"
Five killed in Sylhet road crash,"Four people of a family among five were killed as a truck hit an auto-rickshaw on Sylhet-Tamabil highway in Ferry Ghat area of Jaintiapur upazila in Sylhet on Sunday. The deceased were not identified immediately. According to police the accident took place at around 6:45am on Sunday. Four passengers and the auto-rickshaw driver died on the spot. Jaintiapur police officer-in-charge (OC) Dastagir Ahmed said, rescue work was underway at the scene.","[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sylhet', 'GPE'), ('Ferry Ghat', 'LOC'), ('Jaintiapur', 'GPE'), ('Sylhet', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('around 6:45am on', 'TIME'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jaintiapur', 'GPE'), ('Dastagir Ahmed', 'PERSON')]"
3 killed in Jhenaidah road crash,"Three people were killed and four others injured in a road accident on Jhenaidah-Kushtia highway on Wednesday. The deceased were identified as Tahura Khatun 25, wife of Fazlur Rahman of Fulhari village in Shailkupar; Tuhin, 28, son of Chhabur Ali of Gokulnagar village in the same upazila; and Renu Khatun, reports UNB. Shailkupa police station officer-in-charge Jahangir Alam said the accident took place when a private car hit a three wheeler at Dudhsar in Shailkupa around 2:45 pm, leaving Renu dead on the spot and six others injured. Members of the Shailkupa fire service rushed to the spot and admitted the injured to Jhenaidah Sadar Hospital where Tahura and Tuhin died.","[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jhenaidah', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Tahura Khatun', 'PERSON'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('Fazlur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('Fulhari', 'GPE'), ('Shailkupar', 'GPE'), ('Tuhin', 'PERSON'), ('28', 'DATE'), ('Chhabur Ali', 'PERSON'), ('Gokulnagar', 'GPE'), ('Renu Khatun', 'PERSON'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Shailkupa', 'GPE'), ('Jahangir Alam', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dudhsar', 'GPE'), ('Shailkupa', 'GPE'), ('around 2:45 pm', 'TIME'), ('Renu', 'PERSON'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Shailkupa', 'GPE'), ('Jhenaidah Sadar Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Tahura', 'PERSON'), ('Tuhin', 'PERSON')]"
1 killed in Sylhet road crash,"At least one person was killed Tuesday in a collision between a truck and an auto-rickshaw in Sylhet’s Golapganj. The deceased was the CNG auto-rickshaw driver Saju Mia (18), son of Almas Ali of Sherpur village under Golappur upazila. The accident occurred on the Sylhet-Zakiganj road in Chowghari area of the upazila at around 11:00 am when truck carrying sandstone hit Saju’s auto-rickshaw. Seriously injured Saju was rushed to Upazila Health Complex. As his condition deteriorated, he was transferred to Sylhet Osmani Medical College Hospital where he died at around 3:00pm while undergoing treatment. Golapganj Model Police Station officer-in-charge Mohammad Harunur Rashid Chowdhury said that the police had visited the spot after receiving the news.","[('At least one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Sylhet', 'GPE'), ('Golapganj', 'GPE'), ('Saju Mia', 'PERSON'), ('18', 'DATE'), ('Almas Ali', 'PERSON'), ('Sherpur', 'GPE'), ('Golappur', 'GPE'), ('Sylhet-Zakiganj road', 'LOC'), ('Chowghari area', 'LOC'), ('around 11:00 am', 'TIME'), ('Saju', 'PERSON'), ('Saju', 'PERSON'), ('Upazila Health Complex', 'FAC'), ('Sylhet Osmani Medical College Hospital', 'ORG'), ('around 3:00pm while undergoing', 'TIME'), ('Golapganj', 'GPE'), ('Mohammad Harunur Rashid Chowdhury', 'PERSON')]"
2 motorcyclists killed in Natore road crash,"Two motorcyclists were killed while another sustained injuries when a truck hit a motorbike near Old Ferryghat in Singra upazila of Natore district on Saturday, reports UNB. The deceased were identified as Khalilur Rahman and Belal. The accident took place in the morning, when the truck hit a motorbike with three riders, leaving two of them dead on the spot. The motorbike was heading towards Bogura from Natore, said Singra police station sub-inspector Kishore Kumar Roy. The injured were taken to Singra Upazila Health Complex, he added.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Old Ferryghat', 'LOC'), ('Singra', 'GPE'), ('Natore', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Khalilur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('Belal', 'PERSON'), ('the morning', 'TIME'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bogura', 'GPE'), ('Natore', 'GPE'), ('Singra', 'GPE'), ('Kishore Kumar Roy', 'PERSON'), ('Singra Upazila Health Complex', 'FAC')]"
Pabna road crash leaves 3 dead,"Three people were killed and six others injured when a truck overturned at Chargargari Alhaz intersection in Ishwardi upazila of Pabna on Sunday night, reports UNB. The deceased were identified as Jubbar Pramanik, Matier Shah of Ishwardi upazila and Shukur Ali of Joypurhat district. The accident took place around 11:00pm when the banana-laden truck from Lakshmikunda overturned after its driver lost control, leaving three dead on the spot and six others injured, said Mohammad Asaduzzaman, officer-in-charge of Ishwardi Police Station. The injured were taken to Pabna General Hospital.","[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chargargari Alhaz', 'LOC'), ('Ishwardi', 'GPE'), ('Pabna', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Jubbar Pramanik', 'PERSON'), ('Matier Shah', 'PERSON'), ('Ishwardi', 'GPE'), ('Shukur Ali', 'PERSON'), ('Joypurhat', 'GPE'), ('11:00pm when the banana', 'TIME'), ('Lakshmikunda', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mohammad Asaduzzaman', 'PERSON'), ('Ishwardi Police Station', 'ORG'), ('Pabna General Hospital', 'ORG')]"
"2 killed, 10 injured in Satkhira road crash","Two were killed and 10 others injured as two pick-up vans collided head-on on Satkhira-Khulna highway in Subhashini area of Tala upazila on Saturday, reports UNB. The deceased were identified as brick kiln workers Munna, 25, from Jafarpur village and Shafiqul Islam,34, son-in-law Basar Gazi of the same village. According to the witnesses, 20 to 22 brick kiln workers were returning to their village in a pick-up van in Kaliganj from a brick field in Shariatpur area. The pick-up carrying the workers collided head-on with another pick-up van coming from the opposite direction and overturned on the road, leaving two people dead. The injured were taken to Satkhira Sadar Hospital, said highway police inspector Nasir Uddin Majudar. Later, the injured were shifted to Satkhira Medical College and Hospital.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Satkhira-Khulna highway', 'FAC'), ('Subhashini', 'GPE'), ('Tala upazila', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Munna', 'PERSON'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('Jafarpur', 'GPE'), ('Shafiqul Islam,34', 'PERSON'), ('Basar Gazi', 'PERSON'), ('20 to', 'CARDINAL'), ('22', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kaliganj', 'GPE'), ('Shariatpur', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Satkhira Sadar Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Nasir Uddin Majudar', 'PERSON'), ('Satkhira Medical College and Hospital', 'ORG')]"
Freedom Fighter killed in Khulna road crash,"A man was killed after a mini truck collided head-on with a battery-run auto-rickshaw in Ajgora area of Terokhada upazila in Khulna on Monday afternoon, reports UNB. The deceased was identified as Salam Sardar, 80, a freedom fighter and resident of Dakshinpara area of the upazila. Officer-in-Charge of Terokhada Police Station Mohammad Golam Mostafa said a mini truck hit an auto-rickshaw causing it to crush into a roadside tree killing the elderly man on the spot. Police have seized the mini truck, OC said.","[('Ajgora', 'GPE'), ('Terokhada', 'GPE'), ('Khulna', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('afternoon', 'TIME'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Salam Sardar', 'PERSON'), ('80', 'DATE'), ('Dakshinpara', 'GPE'), ('Terokhada Police Station', 'ORG'), ('Mohammad Golam Mostafa', 'PERSON')]"
Rajshahi road crash leaves 2 dead,"Two people were killed when a truck hit a van on Rajshahi-Dhaka highway at Jewpara Borosenbagh in Puthia upazila of Rajshahi district on Monday, UNB reports. The deceased were identified as Abdus Samad, 60, a farmer of Sultanpur in Natore district and Shahidul Islam, 45. The accident occurred around 6:30 am when the Rajshahi-bound truck hit the garlic-laden van, leaving the van puller and a passenger dead on the spot, said officer-in-charge of Paba Highway Police Station Lutfur Rahman. Police could not arrest the driver and the helper of the truck as they managed to flee the scene leaving behind the truck at the scene. On information, police recovered the bodies and sent those to local hospital.","[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rajshahi', 'GPE'), ('Jewpara Borosenbagh', 'GPE'), ('Puthia', 'GPE'), ('Rajshahi', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('Abdus Samad', 'PERSON'), ('60', 'DATE'), ('Sultanpur', 'GPE'), ('Natore', 'GPE'), ('Shahidul Islam', 'PERSON'), ('45', 'DATE'), ('6:30 am', 'TIME'), ('Rajshahi', 'GPE'), ('Paba Highway Police Station', 'ORG'), ('Lutfur Rahman', 'PERSON')]"
4 killed in Nawabganj road crash,"Four people were killed in a road accident on Dhaka-Nawabganj road on Sunday morning, reports UNB. One of the deceased was identified as auto-rickshaw driver Uzzal, 27,of Mugarchar of Keraniganj. The identities of three auto rickshaw passengers, aged between 25 to 40 years, could not be known yet. The accident took place as a covered van hit a CNG-run auto-rickshaw from behind near Tulshikhani bridge at around 7:00am, said highway police. The covered van managed to flee after the incident. Witnesses say the unidentified victims came here from Rangpur to work as farm labourer. Hearing the news over enforcement of lockdown, they were returning to their village, he said. Nawabganj police said Srinagar police will take necessary steps as the accident occurred in Srinagagar area.","[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('UNB', 'ORG'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Uzzal', 'PERSON'), ('Mugarchar', 'PERSON'), ('Keraniganj', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('between 25 to 40 years', 'DATE'), ('CNG', 'ORG'), ('Tulshikhani bridge', 'FAC'), ('around 7:00am, said', 'TIME'), ('Rangpur', 'GPE'), ('Nawabganj', 'GPE'), ('Srinagar', 'GPE'), ('Srinagagar', 'GPE')]"
"Wife killed, husband injured in city road crash","A 23-year-old woman was killed while her husband escaped with minor injuries as their private car went on the pavement puncturing its wheels at Modhubagh of Hatirjheel on Saturday, police and witnesses said. “Wife Jhilik died on the spot . . . Her husband Sadik Alam, who was then driving the car, received injuries in the accident that took place at Ambagan area of Modhubagh under Hatirjheel police station,” sub inspector Golam Quddus of Hatijheel police station told BSS. Inspector Mohammad Bacchu Mia, in-charge of Dhaka Medical College and Hospital (DMCH) police outpost, told this news agency that the body was sent to DMCH morgue while the injured husband was undergoing treatment at the hospital. The husband said he was going to hospital for his wife’s treatment.","[('23-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Modhubagh', 'GPE'), ('Hatirjheel', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Jhilik', 'PERSON'), ('Sadik Alam', 'PERSON'), ('Ambagan', 'LOC'), ('Modhubagh', 'GPE'), ('Hatirjheel', 'GPE'), ('Golam Quddus', 'PERSON'), ('Hatijheel', 'GPE'), ('BSS', 'ORG'), ('Mohammad Bacchu Mia', 'PERSON'), ('Dhaka Medical College and Hospital', 'ORG'), ('DMCH', 'ORG'), ('DMCH', 'ORG')]"
